<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Deer Tick Killers]]></title><description><![CDATA[Leverage Gatsby Business Starter for your Business.]]></description><link>https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined</link><image><url>https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined/icons/icon-512x512.png</url><title>Deer Tick Killers</title><link>https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined</link></image><generator>GatsbyJS Business Starter</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:19:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><author><![CDATA[Vaibhav Sharma]]></author><copyright><![CDATA[Copyright © Gatsby Starter Business 2018. All Rights Reserved.]]></copyright><item><title><![CDATA[We Kill Ticks with Birds Who Like Eating Ticks]]></title><description><![CDATA[We have teams of thousands of birds that literally walk around all day eating ticks. We can cover miles of land a day given the opportunity to cleanse your community. Our birds are happy. They walk around all day eating bugs. Chickens and guineafowl love to do that. These are happy psycho-murdering birds.]]></description><link>https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined/blog/we-kill-ticks-with-birds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined/blog/we-kill-ticks-with-birds/</guid><category><![CDATA[chicken]]></category><category><![CDATA[guineafowl]]></category><category><![CDATA[tick]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Vaibhav Sharma]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We have teams of thousands of birds that literally walk around all day eating ticks. We can cover miles of land a day given the opportunity to cleanse your community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our birds are happy. They walk around all day eating bugs. Chickens and guineafowl love to do that. These are happy psycho-murdering birds.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We Kill Deer When Appropriate]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ticks depend on deer to survive in their second year of life. They are also over populated in most of the United States. In regions with high deer-tick populations, it is guaranteed there are high amounts of deer! We are not talking about Bambi here. We are talking about large, strong, fast, and overfed deer who continue to over-populate because of climate, environmental, and predator-less eco…]]></description><link>https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined/blog/we-kill-deer-with-trained-hunters-with-crossbows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://deertickkillers.github.ioundefined/blog/we-kill-deer-with-trained-hunters-with-crossbows/</guid><category><![CDATA[deer]]></category><category><![CDATA[crossbow]]></category><category><![CDATA[tick]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Vaibhav Sharma]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Ticks depend on deer to survive in their second year of life. They are also over populated in most of the United States. In regions with high deer-tick populations, it is guaranteed there are high amounts of deer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are not talking about Bambi here. We are talking about large, strong, fast, and overfed deer who continue to over-populate because of climate, environmental, and predator-less eco-systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a trained team of deer hunters with crossbows who literally kill as many deer as they are allowed to in a safe and sustainable fashion.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>